<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title> Logo Golf Tees - www.tee-guard.com</title>
<link>http://www.tee-guard.com</link>
<description>The challenge then was to come up with a Tee-Guard so as to extend the wood tee\'s lifespan, but in no way change or alter the ball flight. All the characteristics of playing with a wood tee would have to remain the same. Tee-Guard would have to be light, durable, withstand high impact, and be highly visible.</description>
<language>en-us</language>

<item>
	    <title> Logo Golf Tees - www.tee-guard.com</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/welcome_htm.htm</link>
		<description>Tee\'s will not eject from Tee Guard upon impact. This is achieved through our priority, internal locking fins. These locking fins allow for easy insertion and extraction, which is another plus for Tee-Guard. Since Tee Shank diameters are different from one tee to the next, Tee-Guard was designed to accept and lock onto Tee\'s ranging from .160 through .180 shank diameter.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "true">http://www.tee-guard.com/welcome_htm.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - The 19th Hole</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/19th-hole.htm</link>
		<description>I don’t know if I have the record or not, but it has been 4 months, and I have used only one tee, and I golf once a week! I like the fact that I don’t have to carry a bunch of tee’s…I carry one in my pocket the entire round I was impressed with how it did not alter the playability of my tee\'s I have found that pushing a tee into Tee-Guard was easy</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/19th-hole.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Launcher Tee II</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/products-launcher_tee_II.htm</link>
		<description>This version has all the fine attributes of Launcher Tee in addition to the benefit of a repeatable perfect ball height. </description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/products-launcher_tee_II.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Golf Lingo Pg2</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/golf-lingo-2.htm</link>
		<description>MULLIGAN- This is allowing a golfer to take a second shot without counting the first stroke. Mulligans are most commonly played on the first tee, or played as one mulligan per nine holes.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/golf-lingo-2.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Products</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/products.htm</link>
		<description>The challenge then was to come up with a Tee-Guard so as to extend the wood tee\'s lifespan, but in no way change or alter the ball flight. All the characteristics of playing with a wood tee would have to remain the same.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/products.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Contact Us</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/contact.htm</link>
		<description>If you have any questions or comments about Tee Guard, please contact us.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/contact.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Media Release</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/media-release.htm</link>
		<description>One of the key elements is that technology has finally reached the Tee! We have the best hitting surface available, and this does indeed improve a golf shot, giving it the optimum performance. Our Aero Space Engineer came up with the shape and the composite material, to form Launcher Tee.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/media-release.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Test Results</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/test-results.htm</link>
		<description>Launcher Tees Ball Speed was an increase of 1.32mph faster off the tee. There was an increased Launch Angle of 1.08 degrees. The ball Spin off Launcher Tee was 362 RPM\'s less then the standard wooden tee.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/test-results.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - April Newsletter</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/april-newsletter.htm</link>
		<description>Our Graphics are 100% complete. What is shown on the left - is close to what the finished product looks like. We are happy that in our first week, we received close to 3000 orders for the 4 pack. Many of our key distributors will now begin the process of presenting Launcher into the RETAIL stores.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/april-newsletter.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Testimonials</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/testimonials.htm</link>
		<description>So, I played a few weeks ago using the Launcher Tee. I was hitting drives further and straighter but really didn\'t attribute it to the tee. A few days later, I played a second round with the same results, longer, straighter tee shots. I thought to myself, could it be the tee?</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/testimonials.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Tee-Guard Story</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/products-tee-guard_story.htm</link>
		<description>the goal has been achieved and surpassed. So, it does not matter if you are a beginner or seasoned player, man, woman, Junior or Senior golfer, Tee-Guard will work for you! </description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/products-tee-guard_story.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Launcher Tee</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/products-launcher_tee.htm</link>
		<description>The extreme distance and durability of Launcher Tee\'s makes it, without a doubt, the best tee on the market today!</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/products-launcher_tee.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Golf Lingo Pg1</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/golf-lingo.htm</link>
		<description>Using the club you\'ll be teeing off with, the object is to knock your ball across the tee box, hitting the far tee marker; then back to the side you started on, hitting that tee marker; then take aim at your partners\' golf balls, eliminating them by hitting their golf balls with yours. If you hit the target with your first try, you go again and again until you miss. If you miss with your first try, the next member of the group goes, and so on, taking turns. </description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/golf-lingo.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - In the Pipeline</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/in-the-pipeline.htm</link>
		<description>Tee-Guard II will have all the fine qualities of Tee-Guard plus the added feature of a perfect, repeatable, ball height. This height has been formulated for all 360cc to 460cc drivers. The molded in limit stop will regulate the distance the tee goes into the ground.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/in-the-pipeline.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Nicklaus Dula Point Driver</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/nicklaus-dula-point-driver.htm</link>
		<description>We were extremely excited to have the opportunity to test out the new Dual Point driver that made it onto Golf Digest\'s Hot List for 2007. There was plenty of hype! So, the burning question was whether the Dual Point would live up to expectations.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/nicklaus-dula-point-driver.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	</channel>
</rss>