<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title> Imprinted Golf Tees - www.tee-guard.com</title>
<link>http://www.tee-guard.com</link>
<description>In short, it is just what the name implies. It is a devise made of modern composites that will guard a wooden tee. Tee usage is extended dramatically, and keeps the same playing characteristics of the traditional wooden tee. It comes in two high visibility colors; White and Yellow. Tee Guard will be very hard to lose.</description>
<language>en-us</language>

<item>
	    <title> Golf Accessories - www.tee-guard.com</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/welcome_htm.htm</link>
		<description>The challenge then was to come up with a Tee-Guard so as to extend the wood tee\'s lifespan, but in no way change or alter the ball flight. All the characteristics of playing with a wood tee would have to remain the same. Tee-Guard would have to be light, durable, withstand high impact, and be highly visible.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "true">http://www.tee-guard.com/welcome_htm.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - In the Pipeline</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/in-the-pipeline.htm</link>
		<description>This version of Launcher Tee will provide a perfect, repeatable, ball height for all 360cc to 460cc drivers. This will be done by having a molded in limit stop regulating the distance the tee goes into the ground. It will also be excellent for advertisement and come in two high visibility colors.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/in-the-pipeline.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Test Results</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/test-results.htm</link>
		<description>When you add Launcher Tees Maximum Performance with its Unmatched Durability it\'s no wonder why many have concluded that Launcher Tee is overall the best tee available on the market today!</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/test-results.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - The 19th Hole</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/19th-hole.htm</link>
		<description>The 19th. Hole represents a place where golfers come together, after a round of golf, and we talk about the game! We would appreciate hearing your experiences about Tee-Guard, and if you would like to give us your experience, you can click on the link below, and include your comments.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/19th-hole.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - April Newsletter</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/april-newsletter.htm</link>
		<description>I am hoping you can tell me where I can purchaser them here in Australia. I am located on the Gold Coast, Queensland but would be happy to track them down almost anywhere. Look forward to hearing from you soon.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/april-newsletter.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Nicklaus Dula Point Driver</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/nicklaus-dula-point-driver.htm</link>
		<description>We were extremely excited to have the opportunity to test out the new Dual Point driver that made it onto Golf Digest\'s Hot List for 2007. There was plenty of hype! So, the burning question was whether the Dual Point would live up to expectations.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/nicklaus-dula-point-driver.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Media Release</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/media-release.htm</link>
		<description>One of the key elements is that technology has finally reached the Tee! We have the best hitting surface available, and this does indeed improve a golf shot, giving it the optimum performance. Our Aero Space Engineer came up with the shape and the composite material, to form Launcher Tee.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/media-release.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Testimonials</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/testimonials.htm</link>
		<description>On the second day, I gave him a Launcher tee and said use this today on every other drive and tell me that you don\'t drive the ball further... he laughed but took the tee. At the end of the round, he walked into the clubhouse, came over to me, and said you are right, I\'m sorry I laughed at you!</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/testimonials.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Products</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/products.htm</link>
		<description>In short, it is just what the name implies. It is a devise made of modern composites that will guard a wooden tee. Tee usage is extended dramatically, and keeps the same playing characteristics of the traditional wooden tee. It comes in two high visibility colors; White and Yellow. Tee Guard will be very hard to lose.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/products.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>  - Contact Us</title>
		<link>http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/contact.htm</link>
		<description>If you have any comments or questions about Tee Guard, please contact us.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.tee-guard.com/sep/contact.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	</channel>
</rss>